dynamiclevels.com 2013-01-19

# Share Analysis Tool, Technical Analysis of Stocks, Online Stock Market

Dynamiclevels.com respects the privacy rights of its users and is strongly committed to protecting their privacy. This Privacy Policy applies solely to this web site, unless expressly indicated by the proprietor such as by including a link to this Privacy Policy on other associate applications running in environments like cellular phones and hand held communication gadgets.

_Collection and Use of Personal Information_

The website collects personal information that you voluntarily provide when subscribing to the website and may include your name, address, e-mail address, etc. This information is used to provide you access to the website and communicate with you. Consistent with the choice you make when providing personal information, Dynamiclevels may use your personal information to provide you with information on updates and modifications to the website via various means including e-mail. You may instruct the website at any time not to use your personal information covered by this Privacy Policy to provide you with information on updates and modifications by contacting the administrators. Please note that if you exercise your choice in this manner, you will continue to receive communications regarding password resets and in response to any other requests for information by you. Please also note that this opt-out process may take some time to complete, consistent with applicable law and operational delays, if any.

The contents of the website may not be made available outside of the private sphere of the end user and/or copied for a purpose other than for private use. Downloading and storage on any computer, disk or other device designed to reproduce the matter contained in this website would also be considered as copying.

_Use of Cookies and Other Electronic Tools_

Dynamiclevels.com may place, view, and/or use "cookies”, web server logs, web beacons, or other electronic tools to collect statistical and other information about your use of this Web site and other websites. This information may include information about the IP address of your computer, browser type, language, operating system, your mobile device, geo-location data, the state or country from which you accessed this web site, the web pages visited and the date and the time of a visit.

Such information may be collected for various reasons and/or for own purposes including research, analysis and to better serve visitors to this website. However, if you have deleted and disabled cookies, these uses will not be possible to the extent they are based on cookie information.

To assist us with the uses described in this Privacy Policy, information collected about your use of this Web site or other websites may be combined with personal or other information about you from other online or offline sources. If you prefer that we not combine non-personal information that has been collected, through cookies, about your use of this Web site with personal or other information about you, then please delete and disable cookies for each browser, on each computer you use to surf the Web.

Most browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually set your browser to disable cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. Likewise, most mobile devices allow you to disable the option for geo-location information to be collected from your mobile device. The help function on most browsers and mobile devices contains instructions on how to set your browser to notify you before accepting cookies, disable cookies entirely, or disable the collection of geo-location data. You need to set each browser, on each device you use to surf the web. Thus, if you use multiple browsers (e.g., AOL, Safari, Internet Explorer, Firefox, etc.), you should repeat this procedure with each one. Similarly, if you connect to the Web from multiple devices (e.g., work and home), you need to set each browser on each device. However, if you disable cookies or refuse to accept a request to place a cookie, it is possible that some parts of this website will not function properly.

_Disclosure of Personal Information and Other Information_

If you participate in certain features of this Web site (e.g., sharing of portfolio and other information), please note that any information you voluntarily disclose through use of these features, becomes available to the user(s) whom you have designated. If you choose to provide access to designated individuals, please be aware that any information you post will be visible to such individuals for their view. Dynamiclevels.com is not responsible for the information that you choose to disclose to other users of this Website, and neither the website nor others' use of such information is subject to this Privacy Policy.

Dynamiclevels.com may also disclose your personal and other information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary: (a) to comply with the law or in response to a subpoena, court order, government request, or other legal process; (b) to produce relevant documents or information in connection with litigation, arbitration, mediation, adjudication, government or internal investigations, or other legal or administrative proceedings; (c) to protect the interests, rights, safety, or property of Dynamiclevels.com or others; (d) to enforce any terms of service on this Web site; or (e) to operate the website’s systems properly.

_Accuracy and Security of Personal Information_

Any personal information you provide to dynamiclevels.com is kept on secure servers. The website uses reasonable administrative, technical, personnel, and physical measures (a) to safeguard personal information against loss, theft, unauthorized use, disclosure, or modification; and (b) to ensure the integrity of the personal information. To help us protect your privacy, you should maintain the secrecy of the login ID and password you may have set up in connection with your participation in this Web site's service.

_Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information_

To access, review, rectify, or delete your personal information covered by this Privacy Policy, please contact the Website’s administrators. All requests must include the following information: first name, last name, and e-mail address and "Privacy" in the Subject line. While Dynamiclevels will make reasonable efforts to accommodate your request, we also reserve the right to impose certain restrictions and requirements on such access requests, if allowed or required by applicable laws.

_Transfer of Personal Information to other countries_

Some of the uses and disclosures mentioned in this Privacy Policy may involve transfer of your personal information to various countries around the world that may have different levels of privacy protection than your country. By submitting your personal information, you consent to such transfers.
